## CURRICULUM VITAE

//résumé

#### Background.

I'm a designer specialized in Visual and Interaction Design. Often working on digital products aesthetically and formally emphasized on reaching innovation and delivering meaningful user experiences.

I'm passionate about UI and UX. I've designed products for mobile, watches, TV, VR & tablet interfaces, websites, and interactive installations. Also skilled in front-end development with some experience in HTML and CSS.

#### Discovery.

I've been working for 6+ years as designer, creating products, experiences and websites for Huge INC, Google, Accuweather, Bizagi, Berkeley University, General Motors, Cinnabon, among others.

From conceptual universe down to sketching, prototyping, mockuping and production. I have experience creating aesthetic approaches according to each project's needs willing for validity, usability, credibility and competitiveness within new markets.

# MAYCK CUELLAR [29 YEARS]

### CONTACT

Phone 301 6454821

E-Mail mayckths@gmail.com

Linkedin https://co.linkedin.com/in/mayck69

Location Bogotá D.C., Colombia.

### PORTFOLIO

mayck.design

### **EDUCATION**







### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### FROM 2013 UNTIL NOW

#### Visual designer · may 2019 to current date

#### Huge INC.

Creating interfaces and design systems for:

- Accuweather @ App redesign (2019)
- Google @ Assistant Website (2020)
- Google @ Chrome.com redesign (2020)
- Google @ SUMUX Google Assistant for mobile, smartwatches and Google TV (2021)
- Huge INC. Newsletter (2020-2021)

#### UX/UI designer · Full Time · june 2015 to may 2019

#### Bizagi // www.bizagi.com

Responsible for creating design solutions for the London headquarter. Mock-ups and final designs production on Illustrator, Photoshop, XD, InVision, Sketch. Design and develop email templates on ClickDimensions and Marketo automation tools. Testing them for responsiveness, accessibility, customization and rendering using Email on acid. Editorial design. Front end development and optimization (HTML, CSS, JS - SEO, vector image sprites, Hotjar, etc. - Joomla, Marketo, Wordpress, ClickDimensions).

#### Interaction designer · august 2018 to january 2019 · 6 Months

#### Ekoomedia INC.

Interaction, UX research and Visual Design, creating solutions for large touchscreens and VR experiences for different projects commissioned by múltiple Colombian construction companies.

#### **UX/UI designer** · **Full Time** · april 2015 to june 2015 · 3 Months

#### Hogaru // www.hogaru.com

Design work for different areas of the company, creating solutions for user interaction and digital interfaces. Design and development of 2015's webpage.

#### Product planning designer · Trainee · june 2013 to december 2013 · 7 months

 $General\ Motors\ Colombia \cdot Colmotores\ [Bogot\'a,\ Colombia]$ 

Ideate solutions and processes for future products -until 2019 in Colombia and Ecuador-, working close to the Engineering and the Marketing Department.

#### Web design and Branding · Project · january 2013 to march 2013 · 12 months

EUCREATES · Jordi Folck

Web interface design, developing and maintenance. Identity design for the European Creativity School.

### LANGUAGES

30% 90% 99%

FRENCH ENGLISH SPANISH

### PROFESSIONAL

RESPONSIVE DESIGN
MOCKUPS / WIREFRAMES
DESIGN SYSTEMS
PROTOTYPING
MOTION
HTML/CSS
3D MODELLING



DIGITAL

# EXHIBITIONS & PUBLICATIONS

Publication of digital project -AQUA-.

Published on physical magazine and Instagram. ISSUE 005.

INK Zine. Huge. [Distributed worldwide from Brooklin, 2019]

Publication of graphic project "thepoisonproject" and "fundamentals". Featured article and cover of magazine.

SCIO Magazine. [Bogotá, 2017 and 2018]

Final university project: "Manifestaciones". Interactive installation. Obtained the highest grade. Publicated on "La fabrica" design book.

Universidad de los Andes. [Bogotá, 2014]

Publication of photographic series "Nómadas", "Exquisito", "Retratos de luz" and "Copy Paste" in the book "La fábrica No. 3".

Universidad de los Andes, [Bogotá, 2014]

Illustrations project exhibition: "Cuerpo en remojo" and "El beso". Galería Guay. [Bogotá, 2014]

Photography series exhibition as best design projects: "Nómadas", "Exquisito", "Retratos de luz" and "Copy Paste".

Universidad de los Andes. [Bogotá, 2013]